<oregontrail>
    <westernmania>
        <item>
            <title>Guns Of The Law (1944) - Classic Western Movie, Texas Rangers</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Guns Of The Law (1944) Dave O'Brien stars as the Texas Rangers help out a family who is being robbed by their lawyer. Watch western movies at ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f6MqwBNiax8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/f6MqwBNiax8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Yukon Flight (1940) - Renfrew of the Royal Mounted Police</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Yukon Flight (1940) - Renfrew of the Royal Mounted Police A Yukon mail service plane crashes and Royal Canadian Mounted Police Sergeant Renfrew finds ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=opwectBHves</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/opwectBHves/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Brand of the Devil (1944) - Texas Rangers, Classic Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Brand of the Devil (1944) - Texas Rangers, Classic Western Movie A gang of cattle rustlers called The Devil's Brand are stealing cattle from a female rancher. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VFjGgVmNc_Y</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/VFjGgVmNc_Y/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Santa Fe Trail (1940) - Classic Western Movie, Full Length, Ronald Reagan, Errol Flynn</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Santa Fe Trail (1940) - Classic Western Movie, Full Length Ronald Reagan and Errol Flynn star in this story of a pair of West Point grads who are stationed ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iQL6H1Iq0uE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iQL6H1Iq0uE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Rainbow Valley (1935) - Classic Western, John Wayne Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Rainbow Valley (1935) - Classic Western, John Wayne Movie Newcomer John Martin builds a road for the town of Rainbow Valley. But bad guy Rogers tries to ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yP6pjnrTTrU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/yP6pjnrTTrU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Yellow Rose of Texas (1944) - Classic Western, Roy Rogers, Singing Cowboy</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Yellow Rose of Texas (1944) - Classic Western Roy Rogers stars as an investigator who is looking for a stolen payroll. He goes undercover as a showboat ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hVoLpkAKGCY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hVoLpkAKGCY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>When the West Was Young (1932) - Classic Western, Randolph Scott</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>When the West Was Young (1932) - Classic Western A surveyor, Jack Hare (Randolph Scott) gets caught in the middle of a land war between his employer and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xkyTbEcp4wg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/xkyTbEcp4wg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Last of the Warrens (1936) - Watch Western Movies, Bob Steele</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Last of the Warrens (1936) Bob Steele stars as a man who returns home from the service after everybody who knows him thinks he was dead. He must fight to ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2jCwemxRfJM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2jCwemxRfJM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Adventures of Kit Carson - The Desperate Sheriff</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Adventures of Kit Carson - The Desperate Sheriff Kit Carson helps a sheriff guard a bank robber whose gang is trying to free him. Watch classic westerns ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EjtL1xXbW4M</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/EjtL1xXbW4M/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dynamite Ranch (1932) - Classic B-Western, Ken Maynard</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Dynamite Ranch (1932) A man breaks up a train robbery but finds out it was staged and the real robbers get away. Now he's blamed for taking the money. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wKCJhEfKgOE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/wKCJhEfKgOE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Renegade Girl (1946) - Western Movie Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Renegade Girl (1946) Ann Shelby helps provide information on the Union forces to rebels in 1864 Missouri while seeking revenge on an Indian working for them ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DGg5rJo7URM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/DGg5rJo7URM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Adventures of Kit Carson - Badman of Briscoe, Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Adventures of Kit Carson - Badman of Briscoe Original Airdate: December 15, 1951 Kit Carson and El Toro go after an outlaw gang that robs post offices. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=310TUG0FUhA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/310TUG0FUhA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Adventures of Kit Carson - Outlaws of Manzanita</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Adventures of Kit Carson - Outlaws of Manzanita The Adventures of Kit Carson was a family oriented Wild West TV show starring a fictional version of Kit ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rWh-Pb0xmo0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/rWh-Pb0xmo0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Adventures of Kit Carson - Enemies of the West</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Adventures of Kit Carson - Enemies of the West A family oriented Wild West TV show starring a fictional version of Kit Carson and his sidekick El Toro. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mbjG3PgUSvg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/mbjG3PgUSvg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tales Of Wells Fargo - Jesse James, S01E13, Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tales Of Wells Fargo - Jesse James Season 1, Episode 13 A Wells Fargo shipment is stolen from a train in Missouri and Jesse James is the prime suspect. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bu3P-d1s-Ks</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bu3P-d1s-Ks/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tales Of Wells Fargo - The Silver Bullets, S01E14, Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tales Of Wells Fargo - The Silver Bullets Hardie takes a job as a security guard in a casino to get to the bottom of a robbery where a Wells Fargo agent was killed ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3KT8gIGfKvc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/3KT8gIGfKvc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shootout at Big Sag (1960) - Classic Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shootout at Big Sag (1960) Texans settle in the Big Sag country of Montana and cross guns with a six gun totin' preacher who doesn't want them moving in on ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MOIzvi6Bxpc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/MOIzvi6Bxpc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tales Of Wells Fargo - Rio Grande,  S01E09</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tales Of Wells Fargo - Rio Grande If you enjoy this movie please click LIKE and subscribe to this channel Jim Hardie has to take a shipment of $500000 in cash ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GQdeJ2sYsb0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/GQdeJ2sYsb0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tales Of Wells Fargo - Sam Bass, S01E10 with Chuck Connors, Michael Landon</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tales of Wells Fargo - Sam Bass Season 1, Episode 10 Original Airdate: June 10, 1957 Jim Hardie comes up with a clever ruse to smoke out the outlaw Sam ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mnTma65aJXE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/mnTma65aJXE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Flesh and the Spur (1957) - Full Length Classic Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Flesh and the Spur (1957) John Agar and Mike Connors (Mannix) star in this classic western movie telling the story of a man who escapes from prison to hunt ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Df84LQA_AcY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Df84LQA_AcY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tales Of Wells Fargo - The Lynching, S01E07, Classic Western TV</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tales Of Wells Fargo - The Lynching Season 1, Episode 7 Original Airdate: March 25, 1957 Hardie tries to help out when a Basque sheepherder who can't ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ljxpMaoxA4Q</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ljxpMaoxA4Q/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Proud Rebel (1958) - Classic Western, Alan Ladd</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Proud Rebel (1958) (if you like this video please click LIKE and subscribe to our channel) After the Civil War, a Confederate veteran in a Northern town finds ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=miaGceBjIek</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/miaGceBjIek/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tales Of Wells Fargo, S01E06 - Shotgun Messenger, Classic Western TV, Michael Landon</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tales Of Wells Fargo - Shotgun Messenger (If you like this video, please click LIKE and subscribe to our channel) When gold is discovered in Pleasant Valley, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SuTl_U-s8RI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/SuTl_U-s8RI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tales Of Wells Fargo - The Bounty, S01 E04, Full Length Episode Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tales Of Wells Fargo - The Bounty Season 1, Episode 4 A man comes to Wells Fargo looking for a bounty on a man who was wanted dead or alive. The body is ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D-t60P-JLmI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/D-t60P-JLmI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tales Of Wells Fargo - A Time to Kill, S01 E05, Full Length Episode, Classic Western TV</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tales Of Wells Fargo - A Time to Kill Season 1, Episode 5 When a boy discovers evidence that his dead father might have really robbed a stagecoach as ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8QAxj9m4omI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8QAxj9m4omI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tales Of Wells Fargo - The Hasty Gun, S01 E02 - Full Length Episode, Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tales Of Wells Fargo - The Hasty Gun March 25, 1957 (if you like this video please click LIKE and share it) An unarmed suspect is shot by an aging marshall ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PFe7eS9A8hg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/PFe7eS9A8hg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tate - The Bounty Hunter, S01 E03 - Classic Western TV, Robert Redford</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tate - The Bounty Hunter Season 1, Episode 3 (if you like this show, please click "Like" and share it) Original Airdate: June 22, 1960 A bounty hunter (Robert ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GRUBAAG0Kt4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/GRUBAAG0Kt4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Caryl of the Mountains (1936) - Classic Western movie, Rin Tin Tin Jr.</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Caryl of the Mountains (1938) A Canadian Mountie investigates the death of a trapper with the help of his dog Rinty (Rin Tin Tin Jr.) Watch classic westerns at ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tVUWxHFgjOE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/tVUWxHFgjOE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tate - Before Sunup, S01E09, Classic Western TV Show, Warren Oates</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tate - Before Sunup Tate hides out in a doctor's office, protecting a wounded man from a murderous crowd. Guest stars Warren Oates. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nRY4BZVKuGo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/nRY4BZVKuGo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tate - Home Town, S01E01, Classic Western TV Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tate - Home Town Season 1, Episode 1 The pilot episode of the 1960 TV series Tate which ran for just 13 episodes. Tate is a gun for hire with one good arm and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=upHfwecuONU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/upHfwecuONU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tate - A Lethal Pride, S01E06 - Full Length Episode, Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tate - A Lethal Pride Season 1, Episode 6 Manuel Arriaga (Gregory Morton) hires Tate to bring in Clay Barton (Ronald Nicholas) to defend the honor of his ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OaikQErMSpo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/OaikQErMSpo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Six Gun Trail (1938) - Classic B Western, Tim McCoy</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Six Gun Trail (1938) Captain Carson poses as a Chinese man to catch some jewel thieves. First he wins all their money at poker, planning to flush them out, but ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PPc-fs4PXTw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/PPc-fs4PXTw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Billy the Kid in Texas (1940) - Classic B-Western, Bob Steele</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Billy the Kid in Texas (1940) Billy the Kid comes to a lawless Texas town and becomes sheriff after standing up to some bad guys. Watch classic westerns at ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d95qvcEeNY8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/d95qvcEeNY8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - The Spanish Grant, S01 E21, Full Episode Classic Western TV in color</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - The Spanish Grant Season 1 Episode 21 The Spanish heiress Isabella Maria Ynez Y Castra De La Cuesta turns up claiming that the Ponderosa is ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h7422x2AAeg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/h7422x2AAeg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Arizona Gunfighter (1937) - Full Length B-Western, Bob Steele</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Arizona Gunfighter (1937) - Full Length B-Western, Bob Steele Young Colt Ferron kills the men who murdered his father and becomes an outlaw. Later he goes ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qKgbOk_qzS4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/qKgbOk_qzS4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Deputy - The Hard Decision (1961), Classic TV Series, Henry Fonda</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Deputy - Hard Decisions, Classic TV Series (If you like this movie please click LIKE and subscribe to this channel) Henry Fonda stars as a deputy in the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6KEa-lH_d80</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/6KEa-lH_d80/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Buckskin Lady (1957) - Full Length Western Movie, Patricia Medina</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Buckskin Lady (1957) - Full Length Western Movie Patricia Medina stars in the story of a swindler's daughter who falls for a the town's new doctor but ends ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WNnBqbhBVM0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WNnBqbhBVM0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Annie Oakley - Annie Finds Strange Treasure, Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary> </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Htadl5ZIffk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Htadl5ZIffk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Wolves of the Range (1943) - Full Length B-Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Wolves of the Range (1943) - Full Length B-Western Movie The leader of an outlaw gang tries to steal land from local ranchers by raiding and harassing them. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zwJqog8EYgU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/zwJqog8EYgU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Kansas Pacific (1951) - Full Length Classic Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Kansas Pacific (1951) - Full Length Classic Western Movie In the days preceding the Civil War, Southerners try to sabotage the building of a railroad. Sterling ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QhFNwHLyR04</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QhFNwHLyR04/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bat Masterson - Stampede At Tent City, Full Episode Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bat Masterson - Stampede At Tent City Bat runs across a group of horse thieves and an old flame asks him to save her new love who is threatened by a lynch ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AOr9UbT0Ako</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/AOr9UbT0Ako/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Wild Country (1947) - Full Length B-Western</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Wild Country (1947) - Full Length B-Western A cowboy breaks out of jail and the marshall sent to track him down uses a comic ruse to find him. Watch classic ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P37oJCa6UHg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/P37oJCa6UHg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Big Trees (1952) - Watch Western Movie Free Online, Kirk Douglas</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Big Trees (1952) Watch Classic Western Movie with Kirk Douglas A Quaker family tries to save giant Sequoia trees from a timber baron. Kirk Douglas stars ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bpx1UKT00J8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bpx1UKT00J8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Death Rides the Range (1939) - Full Length Western Movie, Ken Maynard</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Death Rides the Range (1939) - Full Length Western Movie Ken Maynard stars as Ken Baxter, a government agent who gets involved in a land grab aimed at ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RH-vY5sqXPQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RH-vY5sqXPQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>New Mexico (1951) - Watch Full Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>New Mexico (1951) - Watch Full Western Movies A cavalry officer tries to promote good relations with Indian Chief Acoma (Ted de Corsia). But between his ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HF43EcaKoKU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/HF43EcaKoKU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Jesse James' Women (1954) - Full Length Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Jesse James' Woman (1954) (if you like this movies please click LIKE and share it) Famous outlaw Jesse James juggles a number of different women, ranging ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I2CCRE4JPCk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/I2CCRE4JPCk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Clay Allison, Full Length Episode, Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century - Clay Allison, Classic Western TV Show Original Airdate: 15 Jul. 1954 Frankie gets shot during a robbery and Matt goes after outlaw Clay ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2BP4P_nq_Io</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2BP4P_nq_Io/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Park Avenue Logger (1944) - Watch Classic B - Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Park Avenue Logger (1944) - Classic Western Movie When a wealthy East Coast dude sends his son west for toughening up, he's in for a number of surprises. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=njjqdDYyr-4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/njjqdDYyr-4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Sam Bass (1954), full length episode, classic western tv series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century - Sam Bass: Season 1, Episode 7 Sam Bass and his gang steal a gold shipment from a train that, Frankie is riding on, she uses her charms ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zixl2vEsKqg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/zixl2vEsKqg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Doc Holliday (1954) , Full Length episode, classic western tv show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century - Doc Holliday (1954) Season 1, Episode 10 Doc Holliday, the Doctor Jeckyl and Mr. Hyde of the Old West meets Frankie and Matt and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SsCTcA40N_4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/SsCTcA40N_4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Annie Oakley - Sharp Shootin Annie, Full Length Episode Classic TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Annie Oakley - Sharp Shootin Annie, Full Length Episode Classic TV Annie is robbed after raising money at the circus for a charity, so she lays a trap to catch the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=We0Js-if9UA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/We0Js-if9UA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century (1954) - Frank and Jesse James - Full Length Episode</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century (1954) - Frank and Jesse James Season 1, Episode 3 Railroad detective Matt Clark and his sidekick Frankie Adams hunt down the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=384M8QAFEoM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/384M8QAFEoM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - John Wesley Hardin, Full Length Episode Classic TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century - John Wesley Hardin, Full Length Episode Classic TV series Matt and Frankie track down the killer John Wesley Hardin after he murders ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FQxLUW9P26Q</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/FQxLUW9P26Q/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Joaquin Murietta, Classic Western tv series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century - Joaquin Murietta, Classic Western tv series Original Air date: April 16th, 1954. Matt has a run in with the famous California outlaw, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nR1GDM96dNI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/nR1GDM96dNI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Jim Courtright, Watch western TV series online free</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>After a railroad employee is murdered, Matt and Jonesy go to Fort Worth, TX and encounter former lawman Jim Courtright who now operates a shady protection ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YwcT7ktV2nM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/YwcT7ktV2nM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Annie Oakley - The Dude Stagecoach - Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Annie Oakley - The Dude Stagecoach. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qylidIT38LM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/qylidIT38LM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>AnnieOakley - Annie Trusts a Convict, Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>AnnieOakley - Annie Trusts a Convict, Classic Western TV series When an old friend of Annie's breaks out of jail she must help him capture the other inmates ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FdZM_NQoMjI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/FdZM_NQoMjI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Kansan (1943) - Watch Full Length Classic Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Kansan (1943) - Watch Full Length Classic Western Movies A heroic Marshall (Richard Dix) brings justice to the Kansas town of Broken Lance. Watch ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KoQE4ESmsI0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/KoQE4ESmsI0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Colorado Sundown (1952) - Watch western movies free online</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Colorado Sundown (1952) - Watch western movies free online A rancher helps a friend in need and ends up helping kill him. Watch classic westerns at ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eGwsmAVX-to</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/eGwsmAVX-to/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Riders of the Whistling Skull (1937) - Watch classic western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Riders of the Whistling Skull (1937) - Watch classic western movies After members of an archaeological team are murdered, the Three Mesquiteers join their ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YB2eBB-DREY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/YB2eBB-DREY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Savage Journey (1983) - Full length western movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Savage Journey (1983) - Full length western movie The story of Brigham Young and the Mormons westward migration. Watch westerns on the web at ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iebJ40ARHz8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iebJ40ARHz8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Gold (1932) - Full length Classic Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Gold (1932) - Full length Classic Western Movie When a gold miner's partner is murdered, he comes up with a plan to catch the murderer in the act. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qKvecGO5QGM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/qKvecGO5QGM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bells of Coronado (1950) - Western Movie Full Length, Roy Rogers</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bells of Coronado (1950) - Western Movie Full Length Roy Rogers Classic Western Movie in color When a uranium shipment is robbed, Roy goes undercover to ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M91sodwHRYQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/M91sodwHRYQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Western Mail (1942) - Classic Western Movie, Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Mail (1942) - Classic Western Movie A US Marshall works undercover to stop a series of mail train robberies. Watch westerns on ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q-S2c-_hEuI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/q-S2c-_hEuI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Fighting Caravans (1931) - Western Movie Full Length, Gary Cooper</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Fighting Caravans (1931) - Watch Western Movie, Full Length Gary Cooper stars as a man who masquerades to hide his identity on a wagon train headed west. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4WmHpHSfy7M</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4WmHpHSfy7M/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bulldog Courage (1935) - Full Length Western B-Movie with Tim McCoy</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bulldog Courage (1935) - Full Length Western B-Movie, Tim McCoy Tim McCoy stars in this story of a down on his luck miner who becomes an outlaw. Also stars ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uck0dEQOV_s</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/uck0dEQOV_s/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Annie Oakley - Hard Rock Trail, Full Episode Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary> </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8C24S85rgEQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8C24S85rgEQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Buckskin Frontier (1943) - Full Length Western Movie, Richard Dix, Jane Wyatt</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Buckskin Frontier (1943) Richard Dix stars in this story of a freight company owner who goes head to head with the railroad. Jane Wyatt plays love interest and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HAVPpmYlW80</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/HAVPpmYlW80/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Roarin' Guns (1936) - Classic Western Movie, Tim McCoy</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Roarin' Guns (1936) - Classic Western Movie Tim McCoy plays a cattleman's association agent who is sent out to end a range war. He learns that the shady ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2tj9qQn8QQk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2tj9qQn8QQk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Texas to Bataan (1942) - Full Length Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>This modern western tells the story of a stolen shipment of U.S. Army horses bound for the Phillipines. The Range Busters save the day. Watch western movies ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qFmhBgjQqW8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/qFmhBgjQqW8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Honor of the Range (1934) - Full Length B-Western with Ken Maynard</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Honor of the Range (1934) When money is stolen from a safe, the sheriff is put in jail. When the sheriff escapes and rides to the outlaws. Watch classic westerns ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lIcg1q7P7hc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/lIcg1q7P7hc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Fighting Westerner (1935) - Full Length Western Movie with Randolph Scott</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Randolph Scott stars in this story of a man investigating murders at a radium mine. Watch Randolph Scott westerns on http://www.westernmania.com. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FnogaCwPmT0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/FnogaCwPmT0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>I Killed Wild Bill Hickock (1956) - Full Length Western Movie, Documentary</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The story of the man who shot Wild Bill Hickock in the back while he was playing poker. Told in flashbacks. Watch western movies on ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5pP66yHdljo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5pP66yHdljo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Bill Longley, Full Length Episode classic western tv show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>When gunman Bill Longley and his sidekick Kelso escape from a chain gang, Kelso goes to a circus to get Longley's girlfriend, the trapeze artist Mamie. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gihlIAXOvgQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/gihlIAXOvgQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Buffalo Stampede (1933) - Randolph Scott, Full Length Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Buffalo Stampede (1933) - Randolph Scott Randolph Scott stars as a buffalo hunter who butts head with a group of buffalo-hide thieves. Also known as "The ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wZzdgGWwuIY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/wZzdgGWwuIY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Lone Ranger - A Message From Abe (1957), Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Lone Ranger - A Message From Abe (1957) The Lone Ranger and Tonto visit an ex-convict who has gone straight and become a Lincolm impersonator. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=e96wtQISxQI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/e96wtQISxQI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Jack Slade</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century - Jack Slade. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sWYGbrDIkSM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/sWYGbrDIkSM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Little Britches, Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century - Little Britches, Classic Western TV series Bad girl Jenny McColl (Gloria Winters) is known as "Little Britches" for the pants she wears. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X4dS5ym80zA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/X4dS5ym80zA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Devil Riders (1943)  - Watch Full Length Western B-Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Devil Riders (1943) - Watch Full Length Western B-Movie The Pony Express and a local stage line are in competition for the U.S. Mail contract when a lawyer ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fOXB_rtP6fc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fOXB_rtP6fc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Light of Western Stars (1940) - Watch Western Movies, Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Light of Western Stars (1940) - Watch Western Movies, An eastern woman buys a ranch not knowing that it is part of a smuggling operation. Alan Ladd ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NG8QU4kYhGI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/NG8QU4kYhGI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Sontag and Evans, Full Episode Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>John Sontag and Chris Evans are two down on their luck farmer in California's San Joaquin Valley. They wage a war of vengeance against the railroad. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hHnIZnblXCw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hHnIZnblXCw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Adventures of Gallant Bess (1948), Full Length Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Adventures of Gallant Bess (1948), Full Length Western Movie A rodeo rider tames a magnificent horse but gets cheated out of it by a rodeo owner. Now he must ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UgNjgsvc8NU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/UgNjgsvc8NU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Riders of the Sage (1936) - Full Length Western, Bob Steele</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Riders of the Sage (1936) - Full Length Western, Bob Steele When cattle ranchers and homesteaders feud in Apache Basin, Bob Burke (Bob Steele) joins forces ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O_QTQpA7lYs</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/O_QTQpA7lYs/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Only the Valiant (1951) - Full Length Western Movie with Gregory Peck</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Only the Valiant (1951) - Full Length Western Movie with Gregory Peck A captain on the Western frontier is unjustly blamed for a raid that kills a fellow soldier. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eOdOOFVC_b0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/eOdOOFVC_b0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - The Younger Brothers, Classic Western</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Season 1, Episode 11. When Matt thinks the Younger Brothers are responsible for a holdup, Frankie goes undercover to get the goods on the gang. Watch ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IL1ftazx9OQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/IL1ftazx9OQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Crazy Horse, Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century - Crazy Horse, Classic Western TV series Season 1, Episode 15. When the army has trouble catching Chief Crazy Horse, Matt comes up ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aTj4AgmB1C8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/aTj4AgmB1C8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Billy the Kid, Full Episode</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Season 1, Episode 2. Original Airdate: January 30, 1954. When railroad detective Matt Clark (Jim Davis), sets out to hunt down a group of cattle rustlers, he runs ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_zniY0bfDcc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_zniY0bfDcc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Geronimo, Full Length Episode Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Season 1, Episode 4. Railroad detectives Matt Clark and Frankie Adams pursue Apache warrior Geronimo when the railroad's night watchman identifies him as ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=a7j0BqkshCg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/a7j0BqkshCg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - Bitter Water, Full Episode Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Bitter Water (if you like this episode, please click LIKE and share it) Season 1, Episode 29 When the Cartwright's neighbor's son gets engaged to the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iGgcHWR48mw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iGgcHWR48mw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Dawn Rider (1935) - Classic Western Movie, John Wayne</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Dawn Rider (1935) - Classic Western Movie When John Mason (John Wayne) is wounded by a gunshot, the woman who takes care of him happens to be ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DUZqsoTxvdg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/DUZqsoTxvdg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Brand of the Outlaws (1936) - Full Length B-Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Brand of the Outlaws (1936) - Full Length B-Western Movie Bob Steele goes undercover and helps out a band of rustlers in order to find the man who killed his ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YbnkKr86IPQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/YbnkKr86IPQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Cavalry (1936) - Full Length Western Movie, Bob Steele</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Cavalry (1936) - Full Length Western Movie Bob Steele plays a Cavalry commander sent West in the aftermath of the Civil War to protect the construction of a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=70C_JKesRS8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/70C_JKesRS8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bells of San Angelo (1947) - Western Movie, Full Length, Roy Rogers</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bells of San Angelo (1947) - Classic Western Movie Roy Rogers goes up against a silver-smuggling ring in the modern west. But a cowboy-novel writing heroine ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2OlMM6ynUGE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2OlMM6ynUGE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Wagon Train - Alias Bill Hawks, Classic Western TV Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Wagon Train - Alias Bill Hawks When Bill Hawks visits a small town in the desert to see an old friend. He discovers that his friend has disappeared and people ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AY6ADbN-qbs</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/AY6ADbN-qbs/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Wagon Wheels (1934) - Full Length Western Movie, Randolph Scott</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Wagon Wheels (1934) - Full Length Western Movie, Randolph Scott Randolph Scott stars in this remake of the Gary Cooper classic, "Fighting Caravans". </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oScJ4wYdbm8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/oScJ4wYdbm8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Silver Trail (1937) - B-Western Movie, Rin Tin Tin Jr.</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Silver Trail (1937) - B-Western Movie Rin Tin Tin Jr. stars in this story of a cowboy hunting for a prospector who has disappeared after striking it rich. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lp-bpdJeJ44</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/lp-bpdJeJ44/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - Lost Gold, Full Length Episode Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - Lost Gold, Full Length Episode Western TV series Original Airdate: May 13, 1960. A Mining company wants Slade to find out who is stealing ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZZuyFyw9oU0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ZZuyFyw9oU0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - The Ape, Full Episode Classic Western TV Series, Leonard Nimoy</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - The Ape, Full Episode Classic Western TV Series When a big man with inhuman strength comes to Virginia City, Hoss tries to help him out, but a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B98jHlGA_Y4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/B98jHlGA_Y4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza -  Denver McKee, Full Length Episode, Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Denver McKee, A retired US marshal with an unexplained source of income goes after rustlers and thieves but never seems to find them. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yH-dqSL6Y9Y</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/yH-dqSL6Y9Y/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Capture (1950) - Watch Full Length Western Movie, John Sturges</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Capture (1950) - Watch Full Length Western Movie, John Sturges An oilman is haunted by the fact that he killed a man who may have been innocent. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GOkFHTGgao8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/GOkFHTGgao8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Blue Steel (1934) - Classic Western Movie, Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Blue Steel (1934) - Classic Western Movie, Full Length John Carruthers (John Wayne) is a US Marshal operating undercover investigating some robberies, but ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9qGCKY7-zxI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9qGCKY7-zxI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Angel and the Badman (1947) - Classic Western Movie, John Wayne, Quaker</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Angel and the Badman (1947) - Classic Western Movie, Full Length Quirt Evans (John Wayne) is a bad guy with a bad reputation. When he gets injured and a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ySDAdx4gdj4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ySDAdx4gdj4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - The Deadly Key, Full Episode, Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - The Deadly Key Original Airdate: March 8, 1960 Slade investigates an ancient key that is tied to a hidden treasure. Watch classic western tv ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2bWeeMLJdp4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2bWeeMLJdp4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Lassie - The Painted Hills (1951), Full Length Family Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Lassie - The Painted Hills (1951), Full Length Family Western Movie Jonathan Harvey and his dog Shep (Lassie) finally strike gold after years of prospecting, but ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=USUWmUv4otI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/USUWmUv4otI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>West of the Divide (1934) - Full Length John Wayne Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>West of the Divide (1934) - Full Length John Wayne Western Movie Ted Hayden (John Wayne) goes undercover to find the man who murdered his parents. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2z67mCwTuFA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2z67mCwTuFA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Lawless Frontier (1934) - Classic Western movie, John Wayne</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Lawless Frontier (1934) - Classic Western movie, John Wayne John Tobin (John Wayne) hunts down a good for nothing outlaw to get revenge and rescue a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5PtFBjgIsa0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5PtFBjgIsa0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Judge Roy Bean - The Fugitive, Classic Western TV show, Full Episode</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Judge Roy Bean - The Fugitive, Classic Western TV show, Full Episode Original Airdate: 1956. When a rancher gets blackmailed by some men who claim to ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3okFh52kvKs</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/3okFh52kvKs/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Great Train Robbery (1903) - The First Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Great Train Robbery (1903) is generally recognized as the first Western movie ever made. It is also one of the most famous motion pictures of all time. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xe0Dpfcc9vY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Xe0Dpfcc9vY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - A Flower on Boot Hill, Full Length Episode, Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - A Flower on Boot Hill, Full Length Episode Western TV show Slade investigates a bank robbery and finds a strange group that includes two ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YWeA_XTgiYU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/YWeA_XTgiYU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - Backtrack, Classic Western TV show,</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - Backtrack, Classic Western TV show, When Slade has a small time embezzler in custody, he learns a hard lesson when he's freed by a gang of ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lnMQO_PS0RU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/lnMQO_PS0RU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - Donna Juanita, Full Length Classic Western TV Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - Donna Juanita, Full Length Classic Western TV Show When a land grand company is found to be a gang of swindlers, Slade goes to New ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R4ex7HtLZNc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/R4ex7HtLZNc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - Lost Gold, Full Length classic western tv show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Season 1, Episode 38 (1960). A mining company hires slade to find some high graders who are robbing them blind. Watch classic western tv shows on ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_C8IaKV7wyo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_C8IaKV7wyo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - Spanish Box, Full Episode, Classic Western TV Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - Spanish Box, Full Episode, Classic Western TV Show Slade delivers an intricate Spanish box to a banker which turns out to be booby trapped. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bwWHwkGLk38</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bwWHwkGLk38/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - Killer's Brand, Full Episode Classic Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - Killer's Brand, Full Episode Classic Western TV Series Slade must find the a gang of horse thieves. Watch westerns on ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AatY23fJVS0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/AatY23fJVS0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Rube Burrows, Full episode, Classic Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Season 2, Episode 9 When Rube Burrows, the first man to rob a train singlehanded, steals $30000 from the Southwest Railroad, Matt goes out to bring him to ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NcMcZ8gPl2U</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/NcMcZ8gPl2U/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - The Mission, Full Length classic Western tv show in Color</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Season 2, Episode 2. A down on his luck former Army scout agrees to lead the Cavalry through the desert on the condition that Hoss comes along ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-w1EY8QbO5Y</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/-w1EY8QbO5Y/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Tom Horn, Full Episode, Classic Western TV Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century - Season 1, Episode 24 (1954). Cattle rancher Tom Horn goes rogue after a lifetime of fighting cattle rustlers from the right side of the law. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R1NU4ofMTus</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/R1NU4ofMTus/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - Sudden Death, Full Episode Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade, Season 1, Episode 31. Slade is called into a lumber town to investigate a murder in a casino. Watch western tv shows on ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eo2Tk5T6veY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/eo2Tk5T6veY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - Ring of Death, Full Length Classic Western TV Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - Season 1, Episode 32 (1960). Slade investigates a murder involving a love triangle and a $20000 ring. Watch Classic Westerns on ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A-WyV64zazo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/A-WyV64zazo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>'Neath the Arizona Skies (1934) - Classic Western Movie, John Wayne</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>'Neath the Arizona Skies (1934) - Classic Western Movie, John Wayne The guardian of a girl (John Wayne) helps her hunt down her father so he can cash in on ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eKzY2NC_WWM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/eKzY2NC_WWM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Riders of Destiny (1933) - Full Length John Wayne Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Riders of Destiny (1933) - Full Length John Wayne Western Movie Saunders is an undercover government agent who helps local ranchers when the greedy ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NVXzA3HvUrM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/NVXzA3HvUrM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Desert Trail (1935) - John Wayne Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Desert Trail (1935) - John Wayne Western Movie When a rodeo star and his gambler friend are accused of robbery, the high tail it out of town, looking for the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F3R_I3qr64c</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/F3R_I3qr64c/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Paradise Canyon (1935) - John Wayne Western, Full Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Paradise Canyon (1935). John Wyatt (John Wayne) joins a traveling medicine show and runs across his old nemesis Curly Joe. Watch John Wayne western ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=91ezctiMRuo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/91ezctiMRuo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Trail Beyond (1934) - John Wayne Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Trail Beyond (1934) - John Wayne Western Movie Rod Drew (John Wayne) takes a train to the Canadian Northwest where he renews his friendship with ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=onHzQZC9JAw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/onHzQZC9JAw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Kentucky Rifle (1955) - Full Length Western Movie in Color</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Kentucky Rifle (1955) A wagon train travels through Indian Territory carrying a load of Kentucky rifles. One wagon breaks an axle and it gets left behind and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EdtMOzgrWSY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/EdtMOzgrWSY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>My Outlaw Brother (1951) - Full Length Western Movie with Mickey Rooney, Robert Preston</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>My Outlaw Brother (1951) - Full Length Western Movie Denny O'Moore (Mickey Rooney) travels West to Mexico to pay a surprise visit on his brother, only to find ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VxmhZK60_48</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/VxmhZK60_48/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Hittin' the Trail (1937) - Full Length Western Movie, Tex Ritter</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Hittin' the Trail (1937) - Full Length Western Movie, Tex Ritter Tex gets arrested for murder and rustling in a case of mistaken identity. Watch old western movies ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j5NC3pAWaTg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/j5NC3pAWaTg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Arizona Days - Western Movie starring Tex Ritter</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Arizona Days (1937). Tex joins a traveling show with his buddy Grass. When bad guy Price burns down the show, Tex becomes a tax collector and eventually ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u1Z8b8-y6AA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/u1Z8b8-y6AA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Where the Buffalo Roam (1938) - Full Western Movie starring Tex Ritter</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Where the Buffalo Roam (1938) - Full Western Movie, Tex Ritter Tex returns home and finds that his mother has been murdered. Foster, the crook who runs the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jrEsIy-CYnY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jrEsIy-CYnY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Take Me Back to Oklahoma (1940) - Full Length Western Movie with Tex Ritter</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Take Me Back to Oklahoma (1940) - Full Length Western Movie When the bad guy Storm sets out to ruin a stagecoach line, Tex teams up with the owner to save ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1o_j3LLybLo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/1o_j3LLybLo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Song of the Gringo (1936) - Full Length Western Movie, Tex Ritter, Joan Woodbury</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Song of the Gringo (1936) - Full Length Western Movie When Tex investigates a string of murders he ends up getting accused of the killings. Tex Ritter's first ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oJILEKziteg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/oJILEKziteg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Outlaws of Boulder Pass (1942) - Watch Western Movies free online</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Watch Western Movies free online When The Lone Rider and his sidekick Fuzzy Jones rescue a man from an outlaw gang they uncover a plot to take over a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NgCLqR766jI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/NgCLqR766jI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>American Empire (1942) - Full Length Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>American Empire (1942) - Full Length Western Movie Two civil war veterans build a cattle empire in post-war Texas. Leo Carillo went on to star in The Cisco Kid. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EjfGvnrf6BY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/EjfGvnrf6BY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Outlaw (1943) - Watch Full Length Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Outlaw (1943) - Watch Full Length Western Movies Howard Hughes' famous movie about Billy the Kid and Doc Holliday as they compete for the attention of ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZOl8TJhpm5I</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ZOl8TJhpm5I/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Rifleman - Outlaws Inheritance, Full Episode</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Rifleman - Outlaws Inheritance, Full Episode When an outlaw dies and leaves his money to Lucas, suspicions are raised. Watch western tv shows on the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cgMYWJUoXoM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/cgMYWJUoXoM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Sagebrush Trail (1933), Full Length John Wayne Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Sagebrush Trail (1933), Full Length John Wayne Western Movie When John Brant escapes from jail after being wrongly accused of murder, he falls for the same ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qo7OFpw7Ylc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Qo7OFpw7Ylc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Rifleman - Mail Order Groom, Full Length Episode</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Rifleman - Mail Order Groom, Full Length Episode Season 2, Episode 16 A couple of local tough guys try to make trouble when a mail order husband ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gkDebgtF6Hk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/gkDebgtF6Hk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Rifleman - Day of the Hunter, Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Rifleman - Day of the Hunter (if you like this video please click LIKE and share it) A famous old buffalo hunter shows up in town determined to lure Lucas into ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H9SDcmo1mpE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/H9SDcmo1mpE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Wagon Train (1962) - The Doctor Denker Story, Full Episode, Classic Western TV Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Wagon Train (1962) - The Doctor Denker Story Season 5, Episode 18. Original Airdate: Jan. 31, 1962 When a traveling musician joins the wagon train, it quickly ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KyDz5etzmxI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/KyDz5etzmxI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Death Valley Days - Sego Lillies (1953), Full Episode, Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Death Valley Days - Sego Lillies, Season 1, Episode 16 Original Airdate: Apr 28, 1953. A young Mormon couple comes to Salt Lake City from Boston and they ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yOtbjldK8Dg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/yOtbjldK8Dg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Vengeance Valley (1951), Full Length Western Movie, Burt Lancaster</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Vengeance Valley (1951), Full Length Western Movie, Burt Lancaster. The black sheep son of a wealthy cattle baron feuds with his foster brother over ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4ikJlxN1CO0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4ikJlxN1CO0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Mohawk (1956), Full Length Western Movie, in Color</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Mohawk (1956), Full Length Western Movie, in color. An artist goes west in the 1700s to paint landscapes and native Americans, but he gets caught up in an ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dvKHKAUdwkE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/dvKHKAUdwkE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Drums in the Deep South (1951) - Full Length, Civil War movie, Barbara Payton</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Drums in the Deep South (1951) - Full Lenth, Civil War Movie When two former classmates at West Point unknowingly find themselves fighting each other during ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fn4NHDxr3RU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fn4NHDxr3RU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Hell Town (1937) - Classic Western Movie, John Wayne</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Hell Town (1937) - Classic Western Movie, John Wayne A drifter rides into town looking for help from his successful cousin and decides to stay around because ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ycrs9i253SE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Ycrs9i253SE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Seven Alone (1974) - Family Western Full Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Seven Alone (1974) - Family Western Full Movie A frontier family with seven children heads West on the Oregon Trail. When both of their parents die, the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ePL2bZCzjFQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ePL2bZCzjFQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Haunted Ranch (1943) - Full Length Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Haunted Ranch (1943). An outlaw gang is hunting for gold bullion. The ranch where the gold is hidden seems to be haunted by ghosts. Watch Westerns at ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9EL5lfsD_QE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9EL5lfsD_QE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Painted Desert (1931) - Full Length Western Movie, Clark Gable</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Painted Desert (1931) - Full Length Western Movie, Clark Gable Two partners find a baby in a deserted camp and fight over who should be the father. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xQigCNpYccU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/xQigCNpYccU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - A Flower for Jenny, Full Episode Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - A Flower for Jenny, Full Episode Western TV series Slade serves as a bodyguard for a singer who is receiving death threats. Watch classic ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2RlOFyFhjYg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2RlOFyFhjYg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - Crossed Guns, Full Episode Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - Crossed Guns Season 1, Episode 30 (if you like this video please click LIKE and share it) A crippled gunslinger with a grudge tries to arrange a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jzLlOe5_zD4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jzLlOe5_zD4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - The Fabulous Fiddle, Full Length Episode Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade - The Fabulous Fiddle (if you like this episode please click LIKE and share it) Slade is hired to watch over a Stradivarius violin when a theatre ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iNyjjAWsy4c</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/iNyjjAWsy4c/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shotgun Slade - The Charcoal Bullet, Full Episode Classic Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Shotgun Slade (Scott Brady) is a private investigator in the Old West. In this episode Slade needs an alcoholic to provide sketches for evidence in a bank ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yFQ2CLwY0Ng</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/yFQ2CLwY0Ng/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Stories of the Century - Quantrill and his Raiders, Watch classic western tv series free online</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stories of the Century - Quantrill and his Raiders When Confederate sympathizer Quantrill plans to assassinate President Lincoln.Railroad investigator Matt ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s11LWBFVTTw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/s11LWBFVTTw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Trouble in Texas (1937) - Full Length Classic Western Movie, Rita Hayworth, Tex Ritter</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Trouble in Texas (1937) - Full Length Classic Western Movie When champion rodeo riders die whenever a man name Barker is in town, a beautiful woman ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h7IAoa2vcaw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/h7IAoa2vcaw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Rawhide (1938) - Full Western Movie with Lou Gehrig</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Rawhide (1938) - Full Western Movie with Lou Gehrig A cowboy and his sister buy a ranch in the town of Rawhide but they are pressured to join a protection ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fhdfVQj27b4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fhdfVQj27b4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Alias John Law (1935) - Full Length Classic Western Movie, Bob Steele</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Alias John Law (1935) - Full Length Classic Western Movie U. S. Marshal Lamar Bly is on the trail of John Clark (Bob Steele) and his pal, Bootch Collum (Buck ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XxKub0Rea_c</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/XxKub0Rea_c/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Aces and Eights (1936) - Full Length Classic Western, Tim McCoy</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Aces and Eights (1936) - Full Length Classic Western, Tim McCoy Tim Madigan (Tim McCoy), catches a man cheating at cards. After beating him senseless the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9kZ6eoLK0CA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9kZ6eoLK0CA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Law of the Lash (1947) - Full Western Movie, Lash LaRue</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Law of the Lash (1947) - Full Western Movie, Lash LaRue When the Cheyenne Kid saves a woman from a stagecoach robber we learn that he is a US Marshall ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U8JeWrT06Y0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/U8JeWrT06Y0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Wildfire, the Story of a Horse (1945) - Full Western Movie with Bob Steele</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Wildfire, the Story of a Horse (1945) - Full Western Movie, Bob Steele. When a group of ranchers believe a wild stallion is taking away their best horses, they ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nT494J12eq0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/nT494J12eq0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Cisco Kid - Quarter Horse, Full Length Episode, Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Cisco Kid - Quarter Horse, Classic Western TV show Cisco sets out to prove that four quarter horses can beat a thoroughbred in an endurance race. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=02sn--Tl7cU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/02sn--Tl7cU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Sundowners (1950) - Full Length Western Movie, Robert Preston</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Sundowners (1950) (if you like this movie please click LIKE and share it) Robert Preston stars in this western story of two brothers who lock horns during a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ezdxjh-BKwQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Ezdxjh-BKwQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Border Caballero, Western Full Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A government agent teams up with his friend who runs a medicine show to catch a local gang leader. Watch westerns on http://www.westernmania.com. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8iJBD4Ww3mE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8iJBD4Ww3mE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Six Gun Rhythm (1939) - Full Length Classic Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Six Gun Rhythm (1939) - Full Length Classic Western Movie Football player Tex Fletcher arrives home to find his father murdered. When the same men go after ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ri1_jyyC3n4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ri1_jyyC3n4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Abilene Town (1946) - Classic Western Movie, Randolph Scott</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Abilene Town (1943) - Marshall Dan Mitchell (Randolph Scott) must manage the confilict between cattlemen and homesteaders in 1870s Abilene, Kansas. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=07xpLfHfYq8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/07xpLfHfYq8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Randy Rides Alone (1934) - John Wayne, Watch Full Length Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Randy Rides Alone (1934) - John Wayne, Full Length Western Movie When Randy Bowers (John Wayne) is framed for murder, a saloon owner's daughter helps ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8ngBKEbI0PE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8ngBKEbI0PE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Star Packer (1934) - John Wayne, Full Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Star Packer (1934) - John Wayne, Full Western Movie US Marshall John Travers (John Wayne) must rescue a young woman in order to solve some ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EwJ_Vlo45qM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/EwJ_Vlo45qM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Man From Utah (1934) - Western Movie, John Wayne, rodeo</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Man From Utah (1934) - Western Movie, John Wayne, rodeo John Weston (John Wayne) is in the right place at the right time to help Marshall Higgins ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9XA5vOEd7ic</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9XA5vOEd7ic/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Yuma (1971) - Western Full Movie starring Clint Walker</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Yuma (1971) - Western Full Movie. Marshall Dave Harmon (Clint Walker) comes to clean up a lawless town and immediately runs into problems with local tough ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zNwoz1fo7J0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/zNwoz1fo7J0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>High Lonesome (1950) - Western Movie, Full Length, in Color</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>High Lonesome (1950) - Western Movie, Full Length, in Color. A drifter (John Drew Barrymore) is suspected of murder, when the real murderers are two men ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RvCeeqb6ubk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RvCeeqb6ubk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Texas Terror (1935) - John Wayne Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Texas Terror (1935) - John Wayne Western Movie John Wayne plays a Texas sheriff who decides to quit and become a prospector. Watch John Wayne western ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RxTa_xPJYyQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RxTa_xPJYyQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Winds of the Wasteland  (1936) - Classic Western Movie, John Wayne</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Winds of the Wasteland (1936) - Classic Western Movie John Wayne stars as John Blair, a Pony Express rider who goes into business with his friend Larry ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1ZX92o3jAQk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/1ZX92o3jAQk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>To the Last Man (1933) - Randolph Scott, Full Length Classic Western</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>To the Last Man (1933) - Randolph Scott, Full Length Western Movie After the Civil War, a man from Kentucky heads to Nevada to settle an old feud. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n22ylXYLyc0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/n22ylXYLyc0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Northwest Trail (1945) - Full Length Western Movie, Bob Steele, Joan Woodbury</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Northwest Trail (1945) (if you like this video please click LIKE and share it) A Canadian Mountie (Bob Steele) helps an East Coast girl (Joan Woodbury) get ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vbrMOmY-V_Y</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/vbrMOmY-V_Y/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Sky King - The Wild Man, Full Episode Classic Western TV</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Sky King - The Wild Man When an animal loving wild man is blamed for a robbery, Sky King and his niece Penny lend a helping hand. Watch western tv shows ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XO7aU3TNMT4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/XO7aU3TNMT4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Sky King - Sky Robbers, Full Episode Classic TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Sky King - Sky Robbers, Full Episode Classic TV show Sky enters an air race along with his sidekick Penny, but when Sky learns that the office has been robbed ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SoXkgIsIiQE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/SoXkgIsIiQE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Sky King - Bullet Bait, Full Episode Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Sky King - Bullet Bait When Sky has a wedding at his Ranch, two criminals kidnap the groom. Watch westerns on http://www.westernmania.com. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nOR4afHYxrM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/nOR4afHYxrM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Sky King - A Dog Named Barney, Classic Western TV Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Sky King - A Dog Named Barney Sky enlists the help of a seeing-eye dog to help him find a criminal hiding out with some wolf hunters. Watch classic western tv ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PIDprj1pPz8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/PIDprj1pPz8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Western Movies Full Length Free * The Proud and Damned (1972) - Chuck Connors</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Movies Full Length Free * Watch The Proud and Damned - 1972 A group of Americans in South America have to choose sides when they get caught up ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2u4EhOdEdIQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2u4EhOdEdIQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Cisco Kid, Medicine Flats - Full Episode, Classic Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Cisco Kid, Medicine Flats - Full Episode, Classic Western TV Series Cisco and Pancho team up with a beautiful woman to catch some cattle rustlers. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ivp2jHrcYcg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Ivp2jHrcYcg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Young Land (1959) - Full Length Western Movie, Patrick Wayne, Ken Curtis</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Young Land (1959) - Full Length Western Movie, Patrick Wayne, Ken Curtis In the days after the Mexican-American war, an American murders a Mexican in ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QXFGYtJSlv4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QXFGYtJSlv4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Cisco Kid, Ghost Story - Classic western tv Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Cisco Kid, Ghost Story Cisco and Pancho go after a pair of smugglers who murdered a rancher for not cooperating with them. Watch western movies and tv ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9K0Ckxx7fBk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9K0Ckxx7fBk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Cisco Kid - Confession for Money, Full Episode Classic Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Cisco Kid - Confession for Money, Full Episode Classic Western TV Series A woman seeks the help of Cisco when a man with financial trouble confesses to ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bNJdFG9sMqA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bNJdFG9sMqA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - The Trail Gang, Full Episode, Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Ben and Hoss take on a new trail hand who is using a false identity. Watch classic movies and TV shows on http://www.westernmania.com. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tgo5_24_S0s</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/tgo5_24_S0s/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - The Stranger, Full Length Episode, Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - The Stranger, Full Length Episode, Classic Western TV Season 1, Episode 24 When Ben decides to run for governor New Orleans police inspector ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YjdCjyYatK8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/YjdCjyYatK8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - The Savage, Full episode Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - The Savage Adam is wounded by Indians and left for dead, when a white whom the Indians believe has mystical powers finds him. Watch classic ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pma2WB7UrUc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/pma2WB7UrUc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - The Last Viking, Full Episode Classic Western TV Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - The Last Viking, Full Episode Classic Western TV Show Season 2, Episode 10. A band of outlaws arrives in Virginia City, raising havoc. When they ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GRvZ_JLQ9lE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/GRvZ_JLQ9lE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - The Fear Merchants, Full Episode Classic Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - The Fear Merchants, Full Episode Andrew Fulmer is using divisive tactics while running for mayor, when Chinese-American Jimmy Chong is accused ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hJuSBouuHNM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hJuSBouuHNM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - The Blood Line, Full Length Episode, Lee Van Cleef</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - The Blood Line, Full Length Episode, Lee Van Cleef Season 2, Episode 15 When the son of a man who Ben killed in self-defense arrives in town, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pBcCsLlZSDg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/pBcCsLlZSDg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - Showdown, Full Episode classic western tv series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Season 2, Episode 1. After a gang of outlaws robs a bank in Virginia City, one of them gets a job on the Ponderosa to keep an eye on the authorities. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sMI_oNGFBFo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/sMI_oNGFBFo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - Feet of Clay, Full Episode Classic Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Season 1, Episode 30. The Cartwrights take in a young boy after his mother dies, but then his father breaks out of prison and comes to get him. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bvc625uhipY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bvc625uhipY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - Escape to Ponderosa,  Full Length Episode Classic Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Escape to Ponderosa, Full Length Episode Classic Western TV Series Season 1, Episode 25 When three Army deserters escape and show up on the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mJHkcY1wi6w</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/mJHkcY1wi6w/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - Day of Reckoning, Full Episode, Ricardo Montalban</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Day of Reckoning, Full Episode with Ricardo Montalban Ben gives ranch land to an Indian and his wife after he saves Adam's life. Guest star: Ricardo ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gko033lrVvI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Gko033lrVvI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - Dark Star, Full Episode classic western tv series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Dark Star (If you like the episode, please click LIKE and share it) When Little Joe meets a gypsy girl and falls in love, he must deal with her family and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=06GsmH9sjLk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/06GsmH9sjLk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - Breed of Violence, Full Episode Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Breed of Violence. An old friend of Joe's hooks up with an outlaw boyfriend. Then he robs a bank and kidnaps Hoss and Little Joe. Watch classic ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PJT7aXTdu94</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/PJT7aXTdu94/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - Badge Without Honor, Full Length Western TV Show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Badge Without Honor, Western TV Show A U.S. marshal saves Adam's life but Adam becomes suspicious when he reveals that he's in town to take a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gojOtBx8cMA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/gojOtBx8cMA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Gone With the West (1975) - Full length western, James Caan, Sammy Davis Jr.</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Gone With the West (1975) - Western Movie James Caan plays Jud McGraw, a down on his luck cowboy who partners up with the abused Little Moon (Stefanie ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kTRsV6myOGw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/kTRsV6myOGw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Deputy - The Return of Widow Brown (1961), Full Episode Classic TV show - Henry Fonda</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Deputy - The Return of Widow Brown (1961), Full Episode Henry Fonda stars as U.S. Marshal Simon Fry in the Arizona Territory. Allen Ford co-stars as a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kc--bo7yffw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/kc--bo7yffw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tahtonka (1973) - Full Length Documentary on the Buffalo</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Tahtonka (1973) - Documentary on the Buffalo and the Plains Indians who made a way of life out of them. Tells the story of the culture of the Indians of the Great ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fkEf_kA3f1w</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fkEf_kA3f1w/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Wagon Train - The Malachi Hobart Story, Full Episode, Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Wagon Train TV series. Malachi Hobart is a generous and charitable preacher who may in fact be a con man. Wagon Train was one of the most popular western ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t-Lph6S_RuU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/t-Lph6S_RuU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - The Hopefuls, Full Episode, Classic Western TV series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - The Hopefuls, Full Episode, Classic Western TV series Adam agrees to lead a group of Quaker settlers West, but when he falls in love with a Quaker ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=irNAJ_SV1Eg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/irNAJ_SV1Eg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Daniel Boone - Trailblazer (1956), Full Length Western Movie in color</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Daniel Boone - Trailblazer (1956) Watch Daniel Boone as he leads a group of settlers into the Kentucky wilderness and defends them against Indians and the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wAzvoMWKXw4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/wAzvoMWKXw4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza - Blood on the Land, Full Episode, S01, E22</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza - Blood on the Land, Full Length Episode Season 1, Episode 22 A sheepherder moves onto the Ponderosa and Ben and Adam clash over how to deal ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HSO6BD0HrQo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/HSO6BD0HrQo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Raiders of Old California (1957), Full Length Western Movie - Lee van Cleef</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Raiders of Old California (1957), Full Length Western Movie In 1840s California, the town marshall teams up with a courageous local to bring justice to the land ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ei2FIYSK6Gg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Ei2FIYSK6Gg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Judge Roy Bean - Blackjack, Classic Western TV show</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Judge Roy Bean - Blackjack (if you like this show, please click LIKE and share it) Judge Roy Bean was the justice west of the Pecos. Classic 1950s western tv ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=otzSJOfoOKY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/otzSJOfoOKY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Yellowneck (1955) - Civil War Western in Color</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Yellowneck (1955) - Civil War Western in Color. Five deserters of the Confederate Army make their way through the Florida swamps in an attempt to escape to ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TI5X5zDFoPU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/TI5X5zDFoPU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Rage at Dawn (1955) - Classic Western Movie, Randolph Scott</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Rage at Dawn (1955) - Classic Western Movie Randolph Scott stars as a federal agent who goes undercover to infiltrate the train robbing Reno gang. Watch full ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u21ynRXN_Sg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/u21ynRXN_Sg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bat Masterson - The Fighter, Full Episode Classic Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bat Masterson - The Fighter, Full Episode Classic Western TV series Bat Masterson wins a boxer's contract from his crooked manager and trains him for a fair ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S1V7upBZp8w</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/S1V7upBZp8w/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Joshua, the Black Rider - Western Movie, Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Joshua, the Black Rider, Western Movie, Full Length If you like this video, please subscribe to the channel! A black Civil War veteran goes in search of murderers ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bRmVnTeozqo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bRmVnTeozqo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Death Valley Days - Little Washington, Full Episode, Classic Western TV Series</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Death Valley Days - Little Washington, Full Episode, Classic Western TV Series A Washington senator and his socialite wife move out West - to Death Valley. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w_qEgPHrMGc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/w_qEgPHrMGc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>
    </westernmania>
</oregontrail>
