<oregontrail>
    <wtvs>
        <item>
            <title>Land of Hunted Men 1943 Classic Western Full Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Range Busters arrive to see if they can find out who has been robbing the stage of the mine payrolls. Stars: Ray Corrigan, Dennis Moore, Max Terhune ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=onJdzWjUgLs</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/onJdzWjUgLs/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Frontier Doctor S1E1 Queen of the Cimarron</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Frontier Doctor Season1 Episode 1 Queen of the Cimarron 26 Sep. 1958 Dr. Baxter discovers that the cattle that saloon owner Fancy Varden plans to start her ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XuMDViOrl18</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/XuMDViOrl18/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Courageous Avenger 1935 Western Movies Black and White</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Lawman Kirk Baxter (Johnny Mack Brown) is called in to hunt down a gang of cutthroats who rob gold shipments as they pass through the desert, murdering the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n_4-NdQoBd0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/n_4-NdQoBd0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Law and Lead 1936 Classic Westerns Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Rex Bell plays Jimmy Sawyer, a Cattleman's Association operative, and goes on the trail of his friend Pancho Gonzales (Donald Reed), known as the Juarez Kid ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5cYtULv6cxM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5cYtULv6cxM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Lawless Land 1937 Johnny Mack Brown Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Jeff arrives in town to see the Sheriff only to find him just killed. The culprit is Clay Wheeler. When Jeff becomes friendly with Letty, Clay sends his man Ortega to ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S-XF5UsLcxQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/S-XF5UsLcxQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Straight Shooter 1939 Western Movies Black and White</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stars: Tim McCoy, Julie Sheldon, Ben Corbett Before Martin was killed he hid a half million dollars worth of government bonds on his ranch. Brainard (Ted ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KG4QzDlORbQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/KG4QzDlORbQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Blazing Justice 1936 Western Movies Black and White</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A cowboy (Bill Cody) captures two rustlers and collects a $5000 reward. Using the money to take a vacation, he winds up getting accused of a something he ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8iYW-JR5TY8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8iYW-JR5TY8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Rider of the Law 1935 Classic Westerns Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Rider of the Law 1935 in English Bob Marlow (Bob Steele) is sent undercover to an Arizona town where an outlaw gang, comprised of the six Tolliver ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F3TZw0i0gO4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/F3TZw0i0gO4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Lone Rider in Frontier Fury George Houston, Al St. John, Hillary Brooke</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Lone Rider in Frontier Fury 1941 Having been framed and convicted of something, Tom Cameron (George Houston) heads for Malone's (Karl Hackett) ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=j3ieLrtrLMA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/j3ieLrtrLMA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Battling with Buffalo Bill Chapters 1-12 Tom Tyler Western Serial</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>These are chapters 1-12 of an early twelve-chapter western serial released by Universal Pictures. It stars Tom Tyler in the title role , as well as Rex Bell, Francis ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oKQn5WixvS8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/oKQn5WixvS8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Billy The Kid In Devil Riders 1943 Free Western Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A crooked lawyer and his gang are trying to steal some government land meant for a stagecoach company. The company hires a cowboy to stop them. Western ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1uMHj896I80</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/1uMHj896I80/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Born To The Saddle 1953 Leif Erickson,Donald Woods,Rand Brooks</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>When a young man agrees to race a wonderful quarter horse, a crooked, wife abusing, gambler has plans to sabotage the contest. Western Movie Stars: Leif ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p0qX31YtWVM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/p0qX31YtWVM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Aces and Eights 1936 Western Action Movies Full Movie English</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A cardsharp comes to the aid of a Mexican family. Western Stars: Tim McCoy, Luana Walters, Rex Lease. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cwzbr1yAecw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Cwzbr1yAecw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Bushwhackers 1951 Full Movie Jack Elam Western</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Stars: John Ireland, Wayne Morris, Lawrence Tierney, Dorothy Malone, Jack Elam, Lon Chaney Jr. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=slst89dUFtk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/slst89dUFtk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Broken Arrow 1950 James Stewart Indian Western Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Broken Arrow Full Movie 1950 Tom Jeffords (James Stewart) tries to make peace between the settlers and the Apache Indians Movie Stars: James Stewart, Jeff ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cO_5Y8XmMGM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/cO_5Y8XmMGM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Sunset Range 1935 Hoot Gibson Classic Westerns Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Grant hides stolen money in the luggage of Bonnie Shea who is moving west. Later when he and his men arrive to retrieve the money, they also kidnap Bonnie. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EhVCRk_2_68</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/EhVCRk_2_68/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Montana Kid 1931 Classic Western Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Montana Kid 1931 Full Movie in English A cowboy whose friend has been swindled out of his ranch and then parished must take care of the man's son, then ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ko7YBhYxCrc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ko7YBhYxCrc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Judge Roy Bean Season 1 Episode 7 Slightly Prodigal - Edgar Buchanan</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Judge Roy Bean 1956 Tv Series A woman arrives in town looking for her son. Roy checks around, and finds out that her son is not only in the area, but has ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=719qYrUgt48</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/719qYrUgt48/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Star Packer John Wayne Movies Full Length Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Star Packer 1934 Full Movie in English Western Stars: John Wayne, Verna Hillie, George 'Gabby' Hayes A gang working for The Shadow is terrorizing the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RaPT2wyeuQc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RaPT2wyeuQc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Kangaroo The Australian Story 1952 Maureen O'Hara Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Kangaroo The Australian Story 1952 Full Movie in English (Western,Adventure, Drama) In turn-of-the-century Australia, Two criminals ingratiate themselves with ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yl_frJ4I7qo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Yl_frJ4I7qo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Lucky Texan 1934 John Wayne Movies Full Length Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Lucky Texan 1934 Full Movie in English Jerry Mason (John Wayne), a young Texan, and Jake Benson (Hayes), an old rancher, become partners and strike ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3qPtuFcnGss</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/3qPtuFcnGss/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Riders of Destiny John Wayne Movies Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Riders of Destiny 1933 Full length Western Movie Stars: John Wayne, George Gabby Hayes, Al St. John, Cecilia Parker, Forrest Taylor John Wayne portrays ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lb6IQMR18D4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/lb6IQMR18D4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>John Wayne Movies Full Length Westerns Sagebrush Trail</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Sagebrush Trail 1933 Full Movie in English Western Stars: John Wayne, Nancy Shubert, Lane Chandler Imprisoned for a something he did not commit, John ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=98i3FlBXl9Y</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/98i3FlBXl9Y/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>A Lawman Is Born 1937 Johnny Mack Brown Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Stars: Johnny Mack Brown, Iris Meredith, Warner Richmond, Mary MacLaren The wanted outlaw Tom Mitchell (Johnny Mack Brown) has put away his ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FvQyONn1FD0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/FvQyONn1FD0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tate Season 1 Episode 9 S01E09 Before Sunup (David McLean)</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>While trying to protect a man,Tate (David McLean) finds himself involved in a blazing gunfight. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ofB6zOizXfE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ofB6zOizXfE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tate Season 1 Episode 3 S01E03 The Bounty Hunter (David McLean)</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stars: David McLean, Robert Warwick, Louise Fletcher,Robert Redford,Robert Culp August 17, 1960 A bounty hunter (Robert Culp) is searching for Tate (David ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bdfGWNesG20</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bdfGWNesG20/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tate Season 1 Episode 2 S01E02 Stopover (David McLean)</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>June 15, 1960 Stars: David McLean,Peggy Ann Garner,William Tennant,Vaughn Taylor Tate rides into town with the body of a wanted outlaw he's just killed, and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sVtFQaHIWv4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/sVtFQaHIWv4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Tate Season 1 Episode 1 S01E01 Hometown (James Coburn)</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>June 8, 1960 Stars: David McLean, James Coburn, Hank Patterson, Royal Dano Tate returns to his home town to help an old friend, the town's aging marshal, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fOa2805CUgQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fOa2805CUgQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>1940's Movies Full Length Western Gangsters of the Frontier 1944</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Stars: Tex Ritter,Dave O'Brien,Guy Wilkerson,Betty Miles Tex put the Kern gang away once but they have returned with reinforcements and have take ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M9I754tsVvg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/M9I754tsVvg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Dude Bandit 1932 Western Classic Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Movie Stars:Hoot Gibson, Gloria Shea, Hooper Atchley After Burton kills Dad Mason and makes it look like a suicide, Ace Cooper arrives to investigate. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bf8_y4sObP4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bf8_y4sObP4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bar-Z Bad Men 1937 Johnny Mack Brown Westerns (Tom London)</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Stars: Johnny Mack Brown, Lois January, Tom London Jim Waters (Johnny Mack Brown) arrives at Ed Parks' (Jack Rockwell) ranch to find Parks' cattle ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=or_jz-EnItk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/or_jz-EnItk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Raiders of Old California Lee Van Cleef Western Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Raiders of Old California 1957 Full Movie Following the Mexican-American War, a small group of discharged U. S. Cavalrymen, led by Angus McKane (Jim ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tDieMsrsjgc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/tDieMsrsjgc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Young Bill Hickok 1940 Western Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Young Bill Hickok 1940 Western Stars: Roy Rogers, George 'Gabby' Hayes, Julie Bishop Bill Hickok, assisted by Calamity Jane, is after a foreign agent and his ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=76WT5p68Be0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/76WT5p68Be0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Gun Grit 1936 Old Classic Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Gun Grit 1936 Stars: Jack Perrin, Ethel Beck, David Sharpe Big city gangster muscle in on ranch territory with a cattle protection racket. Out to stop them is ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B9OxsAHiIFY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/B9OxsAHiIFY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Hot Rod Girl 1956 Lori Nelson,Chuck Connors Classic Action Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Hot Rod Girl 1956 Full Length English Movie Stars: Lori Nelson, Chuck Connors, John Smith When his younger brother, Steve (Del Erickson), is killed racing a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M9NtZh0L9bg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/M9NtZh0L9bg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Rio Rattler 1935 Full Movie Tom Tyler Westerns Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary> </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fCBZoQEgrSY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fCBZoQEgrSY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Hellfire Austin 1932 Western Classic Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Movie Stars: Ken Maynard, Ivy Merton, Nat Pendleton Heading west, Ken and Bouncer end up at the Brooks ranch where Ken is to ride Tarzan in the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WUVe84SduSE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WUVe84SduSE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Cowboy Holiday 1934 Western Action Movies Full Movie English</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Stars: Guinn 'Big Boy' Williams, Janet Chandler, Julian Rivero A cowboy tries to help his lawman friend, who will lose his job if he doesn't bring in a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NdY30ukPH2A</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/NdY30ukPH2A/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Cavalcade of the West 1936 Old Classic Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Stars: Hoot Gibson, Rex Lease, Marion Shilling Two brothers are separated when young. One becomes the pony express rider Clint Knox and the other ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qNbEDc7qAmE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/qNbEDc7qAmE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Phantom Cowboy 1935 Western Full Movie In English</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Phantom Cowboy 1935 Bill Collins meets up with his look-alike the Phantom and is soon involved in his fight with Buck Houston. Houston has a big robbery ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mi6Tl9YZE28</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/mi6Tl9YZE28/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Man from Utah 1934 John Wayne Movies Full Length Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Man from Utah 1934 Western Movie Stars:John Wayne (The Duke), Polly Ann Young, Anita Campillo In a horse-riding rodeo contest bad guys want John ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=q1WJydwsrJw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/q1WJydwsrJw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Private Snuffy Smith 1940's Movies Full Length Comedy</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Private Snuffy Smith 1942 Comedy/Romance/war Snuffy Smith, Moonshining Hillbilly, grows tired of dodging revenue agents, headed by Cooper, and decides to ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k432v26rkcg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/k432v26rkcg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Branded A Coward Johnny Mack Brown Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Branded a Coward 1935 Safely from behind some shrubbery, Johnny Hume (Mickey Rentschler), a boy of 6 or 7, witnesses the slaughter of his mother, father ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uNaDIR6LA0U</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/uNaDIR6LA0U/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Jesse James Meets Frankensteins Daughter Jim Davis Western</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Legendary outlaw of the Old West Young Jesse James,is on the run from Marshal MacPhee, Jesse James hides out in the castle of Baron Frankenstein's ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y2itSoxIYY0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Y2itSoxIYY0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Snows of Kilimanjaro 1952 Gregory Peck Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Snows of Kilimanjaro 1952 English Stars: Gregory Peck, Susan Hayward, Ava Gardner, Hildegard Knef, Leo G. Carroll The story centers on the memories of ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yEDnTkRkgLE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/yEDnTkRkgLE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>High Lonesome 1950 Free Full Length Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>High Lonesome 1950 Full Movie in English Western Movie Stars: John Drew Barrymore, Chill Wills, John Archer,Jack Elam When there is a sudden outbreak of ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oD7ccj-mbtk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/oD7ccj-mbtk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Drums in the Deep South 1951 Full Length English Movies Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Drums in the Deep South Full Movie 1951 western/war movie Stars: James Craig, Barbara Payton,Guy Madison, Robert Easton (Actor), Barton MacLane, Dan ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9ignMUjGCuM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9ignMUjGCuM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Vengeance Valley 1951 Western Movies Full Length Free John Ireland</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Vengeance Valley 1951 Full Movie English Actors: Burt Lancaster, Robert Walker,Will Wright (Actor),Joanne Dru,John Ireland,Hugh O'Brian,Carleton Carpenter ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WU3kzc50TN8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/WU3kzc50TN8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Kansas Pacific 1953 Old Western Movies Full Length Clayton Moore</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Stars: Sterling Hayden, Eve Miller, Barton MacLane. also Clayton Moore has a small part in this movie as Henchman Stone Southern sympathizers ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rvOeHjtGaT8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/rvOeHjtGaT8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>My Outlaw Brother 1951 Don Red Barry Western</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>My Outlaw Brother 1951 Stars: Mickey Rooney, Wanda Hendrix, Robert Preston,Don Red Barry A young man travels to Mexico in search of his brother, who has ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lf9jY8qgido</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/lf9jY8qgido/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Flesh And The Spur 1950's Western Movies Marla English, Mike Connors</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Flesh And The Spur 1957 Stars:John Agar, Marla English, Mike Connors, Kenne Duncan, Raymond Hatton A young cowboy searches for the killer of his twin ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BF-dzDZTS1s</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/BF-dzDZTS1s/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Texas Terror 1935 John Wayne Movies Full Length Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Texas Terror is a 1935 is a American romantic western film starring John Wayne and Lucile Brown, and directed by Robert N. Bradbury. Sheriff John Higgins ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lx8yBBKun0M</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Lx8yBBKun0M/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Gun and the Pulpit 1974 Full Length English Movies Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Gun and the Pulpit 1974 Full Movie Western Stars Actors: Marjoe Gortner,Slim Pickens,David Huddleston,Geoffrey Lewis, Estelle Parsons, Pamela Sue ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lIzRVlEkLIs</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/lIzRVlEkLIs/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Trigger Pals Classic Western Movies Full Length Free English</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Trigger Pals 1939 Arthur Jarrett, Lee Powell, Al St. John Kent wants the Allen ranch. So he has Steve and his men rustle their cattle using Pete as an informant. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YmZwCeSP0No</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/YmZwCeSP0No/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Salome Where She Danced 1945 Full Length Western Movies In English</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Salome Where She Danced 1945 Full Movie Movie Stars: Yvonne De Carlo,Rod Cameron,David Bruce,Albert Dekker,Barbara Bates The beautiful Yvonne De ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M5mqxSJqTQg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/M5mqxSJqTQg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Last of the Warrens 1936 Bob Steele Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Ted Warren returns from WW1 to find that everyone thinks he was dead. The culprit is Kent who intercepted his mail, rustled the Warren cattle, took over the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QLM2awsBEdc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/QLM2awsBEdc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Toll of the Desert 1935 English Western Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Toll of the Desert 1935 Stars: Fred Kohler Jr.,Betty Mack,Roger Williams In this old classic western their wagon is attacked by Indians, Collins is saved by an ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BF3Zo5vIna0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/BF3Zo5vIna0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Ramsbottom Rides Again Sidney James Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Ramsbottom Rides Again 1956 Stars: Arthur Askey, Glenn Melvyn, Sidney James A 1956 British western comedy film starring Arthur Askey as the title hero Bill ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EPSmhp3RLxY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/EPSmhp3RLxY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Fighting Westerner - Westerns Full Movies Randolph Scott</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Fighting Westerner 1935 aka Rocky Mountain Mystery,The Vanishing Pioneer Western Movie Stars: Randolph Scott, Ann Sheridan, Charles 'Chic' Sale, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KZaRxDHSIyY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/KZaRxDHSIyY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Abilene Town 1946 Westerns Full Movies Randolph Scott</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Abilene Town 1946 Western Stars:Randolph Scott, Ann Dvorak, Edgar Buchanan Randolph Scott plays the Marshall Dan Mitchell who tries to keep things ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v_rZaA2Do-0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/v_rZaA2Do-0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Western Cyclone Glenn Strange 1940's Movies Full Length Western</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Western Cyclone 1943 Buster Crabbe as Billy The Kid, Al St. John, Marjorie Manners,Glenn Strange Billy the Kid and Fuzzy Jones frame a holdup of the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dhaMfAtYdo8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/dhaMfAtYdo8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Steve Mcqueen Movies The Saint Louis Bank Robbery David Clarke</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Saint Louis Bank Robbery 1959 Full Length Stars: Steve McQueen, Crahan Denton, David Clarke, James Dukas, Molly McCarthy Steve McQueen stars in a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nWxLgnT5abk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/nWxLgnT5abk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Helldorado Roy Rogers Movies Full Length Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Helldorado 1946 Heldorado is an annual parade celebrating Las Vegas as a frontier town. Roy is captain of the guards at Boulder Dam. He helps celebrate the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=y69Df5ifOCA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/y69Df5ifOCA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>His Brother's Ghost 1945 Buster Crabbe Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>AKA Shadows of Death Thorne and his gang are wiping out the ranchers. When they get to the Jones ranch they wound Andy. When he dies Billy Carson has ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3y62LSlwF_U</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/3y62LSlwF_U/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dragnet Patrol 1931 George Gabby Hayes Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Dragnet Patrol a.k.a. Love Redeemed 1931 A Prohibition era melodrama in which, at the instigation of his avaricious wife, an honest fisherman turns to rum ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rjYgck8beEc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/rjYgck8beEc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Buster Crabbe Western Movies Gangster's Den 1945 Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stars: Buster Crabbe, Al St. John, Sydney Logan Buster Crabbe Black (George Chesebro) is after both Taylor's (Karl Hackett) saloon and the Lane (Sydney ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W_oSyr14zNU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/W_oSyr14zNU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>When a Man's a Man 1935 Old Classic Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>When a Man's a Man 1935 The story is about a man named Larry (George O'Brien) who is a drifter. He is traveling by train and at a stop goes to a Rodeo. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mqqGWKOrWdQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/mqqGWKOrWdQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Feud Maker 1938 American Western Movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Feud Maker 1938 American Western movie was directed by Sam Newfield. When Tex is brought in to fight in a range war between the cowmen and the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y4qJHcrtguQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Y4qJHcrtguQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Daniel Boone Season 4 Episode 3 The Renegade Ed Ames</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A former Indian chief breaks out of prison to reclaim his son who has lived with a white family since he was a baby. Stars: Fess Parker, Ed Ames, Peter Mark ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g1U9y8XyWhU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/g1U9y8XyWhU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Young Land 1959 Yvonne Craig,Patrick Wayne,Dennis Hopper</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Young Land 1959 Full Movie in English Western Stars: Yvonne Craig, Dennis Hopper, Dan O'Herlihy, Patrick Wayne. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1STU9y2xHY4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/1STU9y2xHY4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Wildfire 1945 Full Length English Movies Westerns Sterling Holloway</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Pete Fanning (John Miljan) has his men rustle horses and then blame it on a wild horse named Wildfire. Happy (Bob Steele) and Alkali (Sterling Holloway) arrive ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7D_R1JJQKos</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/7D_R1JJQKos/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Rage at Dawn 1955 Forrest Tucker Westerns Randolph Scott</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Rage at Dawn 1955 Full Movie in English Full Length Western Movie Staring: Denver Pyle,Forrest Tucker,Randolph Scott Terrorizing 1866 Indiana, the Reno ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YE9enzuMNos</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/YE9enzuMNos/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Hurricane at Pilgrim Hill 1950 Western Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>An elderly man leaves Wyoming to visit his daughter in a small Massachusetts town because, even though she didn't say so, he believes she needs his help. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mxmIJPefpcI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/mxmIJPefpcI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Jesse James' Women Don Red Barry,Peggie Castle Western</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Jesse James Women 1954 Full Movie Stars: Don Red Barry, Peggie Castle, Jack Buetel Jesse James keeps so busy skirt-chasing that his outlaw career starts to ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pkqh4R8d_Oc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/pkqh4R8d_Oc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Gunfighters 1947 Randolph Scott Full Length English Movies Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Gunfighters Full Movie 1947 Stars Randolph Scott,Dorothy Hart,Barbara Britton,Bruce Cabot,Charley Grapewin,Forrest Tucker Gunfighters (1947) is a first rate ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=36V9fwkvNps</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/36V9fwkvNps/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Naked Hills 1956 Western Denver Pyle Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Naked Hills movie Stars David Wayne, Keenan Wynn,Denver Pyle,James Barton Tracy Powell (David Wayne), an Indiana farmer, gets the gold fever and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Eu54LemD-X4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Eu54LemD-X4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Lee Van Cleef Movies Vengeance 1977 (Kid Vengeance) Leif Garrett Western</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Vengeance 1977 aka Kid Vengeance Full Movie Western Movie Stars: Lee Van Cleef, Jim Brown, Leif Garrett leif garrett Aka Venganza Kid A prospector whose ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=odCfnLFgoEE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/odCfnLFgoEE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>John Wayne Movies Full Length Westerns King of the Pecos 1936</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>King of the Pecos Full Movie in English In the open range of Texas during the 1870's, a young boy loses his parents, because they refuse to give up their land. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MveCwXovtgk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/MveCwXovtgk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Forlorn River 1937 Buster Crabbe Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Visiting an old friend, Nevada (Buster Crabbe) and sidekick Weary (Syd Saylor) take jobs on a ranch rounding up horses. But the buyer turns out to be Les Setter ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=euy-fANC9Wo</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/euy-fANC9Wo/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Wild Horse Phantom 1944 Buster Crabbe Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Billy Carson (Buster Crabbe) gets the Governor to let Daggett (Kermit Maynard) and his gang escape from prison in hopes that they will lead him to the money ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yYoBmlgRKJA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/yYoBmlgRKJA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Shadows of Death 1945 Buster Crabbe Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>With the railroad coming to Red Rock, trouble is expected and Billy the kid (Buster Crabbe) has been sent out to help his friend Fuzzy (Al St. John) who is the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VIgFFuymiYw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/VIgFFuymiYw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Buster Crabbe Western Movies Rustlers Hideout 1945 Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stars: Hal Price as Dave Crockett,Buster Crabbe, Al St. John, Patti McCarty Bringing a herd of cattle to Dave Crockett (Hal Price), Billy (Buster Crabbe) halts ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dnG46t-2fV8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/dnG46t-2fV8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Fugitive of the Plains 1943 Billy The Kid Movies Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Billy the Kid (Buster Crabbe) learns that someone in Red Rock is impersonating him, causing a warrant to be issued for his arrest. On the way there he and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G8G044iowEw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/G8G044iowEw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Buster Crabbe Western Movies Desert Gold 1936 Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Chet Kasedon (Monte Blue) is after the Indians hidden gold mine but Chief Moya (Buster Crabbe) will not reveal it's location. He has also hired mining engineers ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cs23i_XksTA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/cs23i_XksTA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Arizona Raiders 1936 Buster Crabbe Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>After saving himself from hanging, Laramie Nelson (Buster Crabbe) saves Tracks Williams (Raymond Hatton) from the same fate. They then travel to Lindsay's ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J0d2SlQq08Y</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/J0d2SlQq08Y/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>My Pal Trigger 1946 Roy Rogers Movies Full Length Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Roy Rogers And Trigger Gabby refuses to breed his horse the Golden Sovereign with Roy's. When the Sovereign and Roy's horse escape, Skoville shoots the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RF1k8L9mUZ0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RF1k8L9mUZ0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Roy Rogers and Trigger The Roy Rogers Show Season 2 Episode 10</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Roy Rogers Show S2 E10 Phantom Rustlers An epidemic of cattle rustling is hitting the small ranchers and farmers in the valley, and the cattle seem to just ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4SvurA5BB4M</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4SvurA5BB4M/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Roy Rogers Movies Full Length Westerns Nevada City</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Nevada City 1941 Stagecoach drivers Roy and Gabby go up against the evil Black Bart who is trying to pit the stage and train lines against each other. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nJIa5MHmW_w</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/nJIa5MHmW_w/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>John Wayne Movies Full Length - His Private Secretary 1933</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>His Private Secretary 1933 Full Movie in English Comedy/Romance Stars: John Wayne, Evalyn Knapp, Reginald Barlow Dick Wallace wants to marry a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hDz694yBFYk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/hDz694yBFYk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Roy Rogers Bells of Coronado Full Length English Western Movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bells of Coronado 1950 Stars: Roy Rogers and Trigger, Dale Evans, Pat Brady, Grant Withers When a mines proprietary shipping a load uranium is attacked ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-pq0LEonDGc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/-pq0LEonDGc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Under California Stars Full Length English Movies Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Under California Stars 1948 Stars: Roy Rogers, Trigger, Jane Frazee Rancher Roy and his boys track down a gang who have stolen Trigger and are holding ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eBi1NeTG7Ns</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/eBi1NeTG7Ns/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Cisco Kid Tv Series Season 1 Episode 24 - Uncle Disinherits Niece 1951</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Cisco Kid 1951 A rancher threatens to disinherit his niece unless she stops seeing her boyfriend. When the rancher is found perished, suspicion falls on her ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o6FZi89IYrA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/o6FZi89IYrA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>James Arness Full Movies Roses Are Red (1947)</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A big city mob boss tries to replace a new crime-busting District Attorney with a criminal that is his exact look-alike. The criminal's girlfriend is the only person that ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L64MuH2sjQc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/L64MuH2sjQc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>John Wayne Movies Full Length Westerns The Range Feud 1931</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Range Feud 1931 Full Movie in English Western Stars: Buck Jones, John Wayne, Susan Fleming Ranchers Walton and Turner are losing cattle to rustlers ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bM8-g3Ue75c</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bM8-g3Ue75c/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>TrailBlazer 1956 Full Length English Movies Westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stars: Bruce Bennett, Lon Chaney Jr., Faron Young Daniel Boone leads settlers into Kentucky, but must battle Shawnee Indians who have been persuaded by a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nNrrG8cmv4E</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/nNrrG8cmv4E/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Rifleman Full Episodes Season 1 Episode 38 - Outlaw's Inheritance</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Rifleman 1x38 Stars: The Rifleman Chuck Connors, Johnny Crawford, Paul Fix, Bartlett Robinson, Dabbs Greer The Rifleman was an American Western ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kl0LIY1HlsY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/kl0LIY1HlsY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dusty's Trail  Episode 6 Western Tv Shows Full Length Bob Denver</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Dusty's Trail Love Means Not Having to Say You're Bananas Episode 6 Dusty's Trail is a western comedy tv show played from September 1973 to March ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9SbwFrWKtMM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9SbwFrWKtMM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dusty's Trail The Cavalry Is Coming Episode 23 Western Tv Shows Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Dusty's Trail The Cavalry Is Coming Episode 23 Bob Denver Dusty's Trail is a western comedy tv show played from September 1973 to March 1974. In this ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RNcG4_D1siI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/RNcG4_D1siI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dusty's Trail Brookhaven U S A Episode 16 Western Tv Shows Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Dusty's Trail Brookhaven U S A Episode 16 Bob Denver Dusty's Trail is a western comedy tv show that played from September 1973 to March 1974.not one of ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SAtiQn7Tvog</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/SAtiQn7Tvog/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bob Denver Tv Shows Dusty's Trail The Not So Magnificent Seven E1</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Dusty's Trail Pilot Episode 1 The Not So Magnificent Seven In this episode of Dusty's Trail starring Bob Denver, Searching for a dentist to treat Dusty's toothache, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0GmUmhI5nLA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/0GmUmhI5nLA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dusty's Trail Phony Express Episode 19 Western Tv Shows Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Dusty's Trail Phony Express Episode 19 Bob Denver Dusty's Trail is a western comedy tv show that played from September 1973 to March 1974.not one of the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9N2w27c4a5k</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9N2w27c4a5k/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>70's Sitcom Full Episodes - Dusty's Trail - Duel for Daphne Episode 5</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Dusty's Trail Duel for Daphne Episode 5 Bob Denver Dusty's Trail is a western comedy tv show that played from September 1973 to March 1974. not one of the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ALRYW7qf6Do</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ALRYW7qf6Do/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dusty's Trail Episode 11 Bob Denver Western Tv Shows Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Dusty's Trail is a western comedy tv show that played from September 1973 to March 1974 starring Bob Denver better known as Gilligan.It was not one of the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W1IV6gjv_uk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/W1IV6gjv_uk/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza S1 E21 The Spanish Grant Lorne Greene,Michael Landon</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza S1 E21 The Spanish Grant Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker, Pernell Roberts When the Cartwrights find out that some of the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HAMy3MBWT8s</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/HAMy3MBWT8s/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza Season 1 Episode 20 The Fear Merchants Michael Landon</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker The Cartwrights are in Virginia City to celebrate the birthday of Jimmy Chang. They soon find out, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uFolG65-ids</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/uFolG65-ids/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza 1x19 The Gunman Western Tv Shows Michael Landon</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza S1 E19 The Gunman Western tv show stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker Joe and Hoss arrive in the town of Keowa Flats, Texas. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2S8OEgRs1ko</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2S8OEgRs1ko/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza Tv Show Season 2 Episode 17 S02E17 The Spitfire</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker In this episode of the Bonanza Tv Show, While riding out on the range, Joe comes across a man starting a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_NoWyuLLHL4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_NoWyuLLHL4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza S02E15 The Blood Line Western Tv Shows Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Blood Line Season 2 Episode 15 Bonanza Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker The son of Luke Grayson is out for revenge when he ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w5al781VBLc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/w5al781VBLc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza The Savage Season 2 Episode 12 Michael Landon</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker, Pernell Roberts While on his way to visit a man about windmills, Adam is wounded by Indians and left for ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TT-9upTMu54</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/TT-9upTMu54/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza S2 E9 Breed Of Violence Ben Cartwright, Little Joe</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza Michael Landon Season 2 Episode 9 Breed Of Violence Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker Joe's friend Dolly Kincaid is the daughter ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jBQEVypRuYY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jBQEVypRuYY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza Season 2 Episode 10 The Last Viking Michael Landon</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza The Last Viking Season 2 Episode 10 Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker Gunnar Borgstrom is the leader of a vicious band called the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AqLxwTyifOE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/AqLxwTyifOE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Rifleman Full Episodes Season 2 Episode 16 Mail Order Groom</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The Rifleman Chuck Connors Season 2 Episode 16 Mail Order Groom Stars: Chuck Connors, Johnny Crawford, Paul Fix, Bartlett Robinson, Dabbs Greer The ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7H2cWVMEOKM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/7H2cWVMEOKM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza S2 E8 The Abduction Michael Landon Full Episode</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker When Joe brings the daughter of a local tycoon to the carnival, she goes missing. Will they find her ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P-DLpqFVJAA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/P-DLpqFVJAA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza Season 2 Episode 7 Day Of Reckoning</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker After being injured in a fight, Ben is nursed back to health by Matsou and his wife Hatoya. In return ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JFZfb2XPH1o</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/JFZfb2XPH1o/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza Season 2 Episode 2 The Mission Michael Landon,Lorne Greene</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker, Peter Whitney (actor) Bonanza 2x2 The Mission - Hoss befriends an old drunk named Charlie Trent, who at ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aVyx5mz7IuU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/aVyx5mz7IuU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza 2x5 - The Hopefuls - Western Tv Shows Full Length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza Season 2 Episode 5 The Hopefuls Bonanza Stars: Michael Landon, Lorne Greene, Dan Blocker Whilst in Virginia City on ranch business, Adam meets ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A1deOoKHp30</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/A1deOoKHp30/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza 2 x 6 Denver McKee Lorne Greene, Michael Landon</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza Season 2 Episode 6 Denver McKee Bonanza Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker While celebrating the return of his daughter Connie, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PyXBWI5cmHA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/PyXBWI5cmHA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Bonanza S02E01 Showdown Season 2 Episode 1 Michael Landon</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bonanza Stars: Lorne Greene, Michael Landon, Dan Blocker An outlaw gang robs Virginia City's bank and makes off with almost all of its money. The youngest ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nZY1dI32f2g</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/nZY1dI32f2g/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>
    </wtvs>
</oregontrail>