<oregontrail>
    <wmf>
        <item>
            <title>the gun and the pulpit - classic western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A young gunslinger on the lam impersonates a preacher, brings hope to his parishioners, and law-and-order to a town terrorized by a strongman's bunch. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=k-lxzZgmTR4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/k-lxzZgmTR4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the fighting westerner - full westerns full movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The heirs of the dying owner of a valuable radium mine are being murdered as a mining engineer tries to unccover the killer and clear his cousin's name. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=roE0ZSFMjVI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/roE0ZSFMjVI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>rustlers' hideout - full western movies with buster crabbe</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Buster Crabbe rides to the rescue of the victims of some greedy rustlers who are plaguing the locals. In true cowboy hero fashion, he proceeds to clean up the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=36hn3On4KH4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/36hn3On4KH4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the proud rebel - western movies full length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A Confederate veteran living in the Yankee North struggles with his son's shock induced muteness and the hate of the Northerners. Searching for a doctor who ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B34iUV38RYc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/B34iUV38RYc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>wild horse phantom - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A lawman stages a prison break so a gang of imprisoned robbers will lead him to their hidden loot. Billy Carson gets the Governor to let Daggett and his gang ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2O9wvNSqv1M</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/2O9wvNSqv1M/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>concrete cowboy - full length western aventure movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Two Montana saddletramps head to Nashville to open up a detective agency. At first, the agency begins on a lark, but soon they get involved in a case involving ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5qtsW_MrxT4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/5qtsW_MrxT4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>gun grit aka protection racket - full western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Big city gangster muscle in on ranch territory with a cattle protection racket. Out to stop them is federal agent Jack Perrin. When things get hot for them in the city, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZXE_Lhjy98I</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ZXE_Lhjy98I/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the dude bandit - full movie free full length westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>After Burton kills Dad Mason and makes it look like a suicide, Ace Cooper arrives to investigate. He poses as a coward during the day but at night he becomes ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FZWE8jLESbc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/FZWE8jLESbc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the bushwhackers aka the rebel - full western classic movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>An evil arthritic rancher and his murderous daughter are having settlers killed to prevent them from selling their land to the railroad. Plot here has Confederate ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h2Gnt6p2MaE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/h2Gnt6p2MaE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the montana kid - classic western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A cowboy whose friend has been swindled out of his ranch and then murdered must take care of the man's son, then he goes after the killers. Larson cheats ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ta7fVkkSpqA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Ta7fVkkSpqA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>gangsters of the frontier - classic western movies full length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Terror Sweeps the range as ruthless gangsters move in for the kill! Tex put the Kern gang away once but they have returned with reinforcements and have take ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c2Wugp6LE8g</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/c2Wugp6LE8g/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>trail blazer - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Daniel Boone leads settlers into Kentucky, but must battle Shawnee Indians who have been persuaded by a French renegade that Boone and the settlers are ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HIAZHajZgnY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/HIAZHajZgnY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>star packer - full length john wayne western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>John Wayne Western Movie - Star Packer A gang working for The Shadow is terrorizing the town. John Travers decides to take on the job of sheriff and do ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9lJKwN54QG0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/9lJKwN54QG0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>raiders of old california - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>In this western set in the Mexican controlled part of California, a villainous cavalry officer is trying to force the owner of a hacienda to give him his land when a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ts1Fx-G5Bhw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Ts1Fx-G5Bhw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the dawn rider - full length john wayne western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>John Wayne Western Movies When John Mason's father is killed, John is wounded. Attracted to his nurse Alice, a conflict arises between him and his friend Ben ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6zZvkqCiSyI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/6zZvkqCiSyI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>his private secretary - full length john wayne western movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A minister's granddaughter tames a tycoon's playboy son. Dick Wallace wants to marry a minister's grand-daughter but his father, who wants him to get work on ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PJdMQ7sZRYI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/PJdMQ7sZRYI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the feud maker - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>When Tex is brought in to fight in a range war between the cowmen and the nesters, he meets his old outlaw boss Lassiter. He learns Lassiter is behind the feud ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0fDl7aLCY9c</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/0fDl7aLCY9c/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the man from utah - john wayne western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>In a horse-riding rodeo contest bad guys want John Weston to lose. When he doesn't go along they add some insurance: a poisoned needle just under his ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=v0w2F14-QWM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/v0w2F14-QWM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the over the hill gang - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A retired Texas Ranger and his three aging pals are hired to clean up a lawless town. Classic comedic western, Captain Oren Hayes of the Texas Rangers takes ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pWMWE25JfC8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/pWMWE25JfC8/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>wildfire, the story of a horse - full western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A magnificent but untamed horse named Wildfire is wrongfully blamed for rustling and horse-wrangling! This 1945 Cinecolor B-western favorite features the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x06wjc6MoRM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/x06wjc6MoRM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>west of the divide - full length john wayne western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>John Wayne Westerns West of the Divide finds the Duke as a man searching for his younger brother and at the same time the people who kidnapped him and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sPUMIFnu5zU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/sPUMIFnu5zU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>kansas pacific - full length classic western</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>With the Civil War about to begin, Southern saboteurs attack frontier railroad construction. Set prior to the Civil War but after the South has seceded from the U.S., ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uWPW085fmTE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/uWPW085fmTE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>randy rides alone - full length john wayne western movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Jailed for murders he didn't commit, Randy escapes only to stumble into the den of the real murderers. Randy is jailed for murders he didn't commit. Knowing he ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cb4W9tcq-d0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/cb4W9tcq-d0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>born to the west - full length john wayne western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>John Wayne and sidekick Syd Saylor are heading from Montana to Wyoming to the ranch of Wayne's cousin Johnny Mack Brown. Wayne's a cocky sort, fancies ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qKaHar9ZkQc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/qKaHar9ZkQc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>daniel boone, trail blazer - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>The battle for territory in the wilds of the old west gets a hand from settlers who obviously want to wipe the natives out, not smoke the peace pipe with them. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=70KydTxbDxg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/70KydTxbDxg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>texas terror - full length john wayne western movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>John Wayne Western Movies Sheriff John Higgins (John Wayne) quits and goes into prospecting after he thinks he has killed his best friend in shooting it out ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FhmqdvRVpTY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/FhmqdvRVpTY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>john wayne & lucille ball</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Mr Mooney sends Lucy to deliver some papers pertaining to the financing of John Wayne's latest production. Despite his orders to drop off the papers with one of ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sC2xlFbuExs</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/sC2xlFbuExs/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the big trees - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Douglas plays a greedy timber baron who seeks to exploit the Sequoia forest, while facing the protest of the Quaker colonists. The Big Trees is a 1952 Western ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZIPCDo_u9IM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ZIPCDo_u9IM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>gangster's den - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Black is after both Taylor's saloon and the Lane ranch. Fuzzy takes the gold from his and Billy's mine and buys Taylor's saloon. This puts him and Billy in conflict ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FnsBVzfxCOc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/FnsBVzfxCOc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>western cyclone - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Billy the Kid and Fuzzy Jones frame a holdup of the stagecoach Fuzzy is driving in order to impress upon Senator Peabody, riding in the coach, that something ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jWpatfLIjBg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jWpatfLIjBg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>hot rod girl - full length action movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>After his kid brother is killed in a street race, a champion drag-racer quits racing. However, a new kid comes to town determined to force him back into racing so ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l9al4xXFzjc</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/l9al4xXFzjc/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>jesse james' women - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Jesse James keeps so busy skirt-chasing that his outlaw career starts to suffer. Jesse James leaves Missouri for Mississippi, and immediately charms all the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_-61uEVzkNA</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_-61uEVzkNA/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>when a man's a man - full length classic westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A landslide has diverted water from the Baldwin ranch to Cambert's. With their cattle dying, Cambert refuses to let them have any water. Easterner Larry Knight ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oFmbXPlVyqg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/oFmbXPlVyqg/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>days of jesse james - western movies full length</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Bank robbery pulled off by the bank officials, not the usual James gang. Roy Rogers has been sent to bring in Jesse James. After Wyatt's bank is robbed and ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bDEnkRUt-rI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bDEnkRUt-rI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>fugitive of the plains - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Billy the Kid and his sidekick Fuzzy Jones get word that crimes are being conducted in his name in nearby Red Rock County. Investigating the situation in the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cm2lYPi1lPU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/cm2lYPi1lPU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>shadows of death - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Billy Carson tracks down the murderer of a man carrying news of the railroad travelling through the town of Red Rock, where Fuzzy Q. Jones is Justice of the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ENi4w05oSp4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ENi4w05oSp4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>kansas pacific - full western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Just before the Civil War (but after the South has seceded), Southern saboteurs try to prevent railroad construction from crossing Kansas to the frontier; army ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jJgbtoWAYAs</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/jJgbtoWAYAs/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>rage at dawn - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Rage at Dawn is a fictionalized account of the Pinkertons' efforts to bring to justice the Reno Brothers' gang in southern Indiana shortly after the Civil War. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MjOoz4IZ6QU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/MjOoz4IZ6QU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>range feud - full length john wayne western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Clint Turner is arrested for the murder of his girlfriend Judy's father, a rival rancher who was an enemy of his own father. Ranchers Walton and Turner are losing ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tdP4viH6sRY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/tdP4viH6sRY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the naked hills - full length western with marcia henderson</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Marcia Henderson looking as lovely as ever.. Tracy Powell, an Indiana farmer, gets the gold fever and heads for Stockton, California in 1849. There, he ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T7bnvtCxC1U</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/T7bnvtCxC1U/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>his brother's ghost - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Thorne and his gang are wiping out the ranchers. When they get to the Jones ranch they wound Andy. When he dies Billy Carson has his brother Fuzzy become ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8DFuxxOx2M4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8DFuxxOx2M4/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>under california stars - full length westerns</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Rancher Roy and his boys track down a gang who have stolen Trigger and are holding him for ransom. Roy has just finished his latest film and leaves for his ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AlS81QaTA74</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/AlS81QaTA74/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>high lonesome - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>When a sudden spurt of murders occurs in the Big Bend country, suspicion immediately falls on a young drifter who just moved to the area. ***spoilers *** John ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uZpfuw_CEyQ</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/uZpfuw_CEyQ/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>abilene town - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Sheriff tries to stop homesteader conflicts in the West after the Civil War. In the years following the Civil War, the town of Abilene, Kansas is poised on the brink of ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DvuzluO579g</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/DvuzluO579g/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>texas terror - john wayne western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>John Wayne Western Texas Terror is a 1935 American romantic Western film starring John Wayne and Lucile Brown, and directed by Robert N. Bradbury. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bV1bR2abdJM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/bV1bR2abdJM/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the young land - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A white man (Dennis Hopper) stands trial for killing a Mexican in 1848 California, just after the Mexican War. *-SPOILERS AHEAD-* In the town of San Bartolo, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sRDYKWHRj6k</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/sRDYKWHRj6k/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>gunfighters - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Gunfighter Brazos Kane takes a job on a ranch but he is unjustly accused of killing fellow cowhand Bob Tyrell and must clear himself by finding the real killer. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ksMq3xwJY9g</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ksMq3xwJY9g/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>salome where she danced - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Anna Marie (Yvonne De Carlo) is a graceful Viennese ballerina as known as "Salome." After a prince she loved is killed in the Franco-Prussian war, she falls for ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XjLjjOfWKFw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/XjLjjOfWKFw/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the terror of tiny town - midget western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>An evil gunslinging midget comes to terrorize the good little people of Tiny Town. The townspeople organize to defeat him, and zany antics ensue. "Tiny Town" is ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dz4OE8qnDVU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/dz4OE8qnDVU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>border vengeance - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A rancher is murdered after discovering that 40 head of his cattle have been rustled. A neighboring family is accused of the crime and flees across the border, ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_7g2KPocUkE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/_7g2KPocUkE/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>broadway to cheyenne - john wayne western movie</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A cowboy detective goes up against a gang of big-city thugs trying to set up a protection racket out west. When Owens' gang shoots it out in a New York ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vo_cxA4LbZU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/Vo_cxA4LbZU/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>salome - full western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Yvonne De Carlo is a dancer who is forced to flee her country after she is accused of being a spy. She ends up in a lawless western town in Arizona, where she ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fGQWGyNODqY</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/fGQWGyNODqY/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>the young land - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>An American gunslinger kills a Mexican man in California immediately after the Mexican-American war. The killer is arrested and put on trial for murder with the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EVtuSizzSA0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/EVtuSizzSA0/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>rogue of the range - full length western movies</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>Doran and the Sheriff have a scheme to bring in an outlaw gang. Doran is sent to prison so he and the gang leader Mitchell can break out. This gets him into the ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E0GQpH-Zrac</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/E0GQpH-Zrac/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>joshuah - western starring brenda venus</title>
            <meta>
                <summary>A black soldier returns from fighting for the Union in the Civil War only to find out that his mother has been murdered by a gang of white thugs. He becomes a ... </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u1SRCYmmlzI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/u1SRCYmmlzI/default.jpg</thumbnail>
        </item>
    </wmf>
</oregontrail>
